# ABDULRHMAN YOUSEF ALSAEED

0566199118 · aalsaeed0033@stu.kau.edu.sa · abdulrhmanalsa2@gmail.com · Jeddah, SA



## **COMPUTER INFORMATION SYSTEM FRESH GRADUATE**

Information systems graduate who obtained a certificate in E-Systems Development track. with proficiency in web development, database, UX/UI design, and software analysis. My experience coupled with my quick learning and application of new knowledge, qualify me for technical roles related to information systems. I'm excited to bring my hardworking attitude and technical skills to contribute to the organization's success.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **WOW Digital Information Technology - Summer Internship**

Jun 2022 - Aug 2022

Dealing with real stakeholders by analyzing real projects, collecting the requirements, creating flow charts, designing the system, designing the user interface, and ending with the implementation of the ERP system.

## **College & Personal Projects**

Jan 2019 - Present

I've worked on several projects during my college studies, including software testing, SQL databases, and networking using CISCO Packet Tracer. I am also currently learning UX/UI design and web development, and have started working on personal projects which I have uploaded to my GitHub repository.

# **Graphic Designer - Freelancer & Volunteer**

Jan 2019 - 2022

Using my free time as a freelance graphic designer to design logos for companies or individuals and design social media posts in a creative way. I also worked on the sports committee at our college as a head graphic designer of the committee.

## **EDUCATION**

# King Abdulaziz University - Faculty of Computing and Information Technology

2023

**Bachelor of Computer Information System** 

#### **Al-Thagar Typical School**

2018

**High School Natural Sciences** 

### **PROJECTS**

# **Graduation project**

Des 2022 - Mar 2023

Is a user-friendly platform that helps students with their senior projects and finds compatible supervisors. The platform is also dedicated to partnering with technology companies to integrate new ideas and help students develop skills that will benefit them in the future.

Tools: PHP · MYSQL · Laravel · Bootstrap · HTML · CSS · JavaScript · Figma · LaTeX

# My portfolio website

Jul 2023 - July 2023

# Tools: PHP $\cdot$ MYSQL $\cdot$ Laravel $\cdot$ Bootstrap $\cdot$ Figma

# Student Projects helper platform

Feb 2022 - Mar 2022

This website helps students improve their projects by showcasing previous work from different colleges. Students can contribute their own projects and users can view and comment on them without registering, but need to register to upload their own projects.

Tools: HTML · CSS · JavaScript · MS SQL

#### **Simple API Implementation**

Jan 2023 - Jan 2023

Tools: JavaScript · Node.is · Postman · API Providers

### **SKILLS & OTHER**

**Skills:** Good Level In (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Laravel, FIGMA, XD, WORD, EXCEL, PROJECT, LaTeX) · intermediate In (SQL, JS, API, PHP) · Basics In (AWS, Azure, Flutter)

**Courses & Certificates:** E-system Development • BSF Intro to Financial Sustainability • Doroob Blockchain • JavaScript Essentials • Data Analysis • Database Administration • Linux Essentials • Microsoft cloud computing • Google Digital Marketing